Guide to the New York University Stern School of Business Collection of Pig Memorabilia MC.234
New York University Archives
- Series I: Single Pig Figurines
  - Subseries I B: Ceramic Pig Figurines with Human-Like Traits
    - Pig in Suit Smoking and Reading, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 1)
      Ceramic pig in colorful suit reading and smoking
    - Pig in Green Outfit, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 12)
      Beige, ceramic pig in green golfer's hat and green polo shirt
    - Pig in Suit with Guitar, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 12)
      Ceramic pig in yellow and green suit playing a guitar and singing
    - Pig in Train, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 25)
      Pig leaning out of green train; ceramic
    - Pig with Bobble Head in Suit, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 27)
      Ceramic pig with bobble head and spring arms in a suit with a cane
    - Pig with Baby Carriage, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 2)
      Very light beige or pink pig pushing two piglets in a baby carriage text on the carriage reads "Wheeling His Own Baby"
    - Pig with Supplies in Umbrella-Shaped Nook, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 3)
      Pig in green, umbrella-shaped nook with basket, mop, and bucket; ceramic
    - Pig in Black Hat and Overalls, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 10)
      Ceramic pig in black hat and overalls; possibly separated from a set
    - Pig in Sailor Outfit, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 12)
      Ceramic pig in black sailor outfit and green tie; possibly separated from a set
    - Pig in Newsboy Cap and Sweater, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 26)
      Ceramic pig dressed in a black newsboy cap and black, oversized sweater; possibly from a set
    - Pig Playing Violin, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 29)
      Pink, ceramic pig with red tongue playing the violin
    - Pig in Baseball Uniform, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 4)
      White, ceramic pig in baseball uniform with catcher's mitt
    - Pig with Collar and Hat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 12)
      Yellow, ceramic pig with red collar and green hat
    - Pig by Well, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 14)
      Pink pig near orange and green well; ceramic
    - Pig in Suit by Crate of Balls, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 15)
      Ceramic pig in white suit with orange vest with clover detail by wooden crate of balls with an inscription that reads "Cul Holz;" cracked head and ear
    - Pig Sitting on Binoculars, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 6)
      Pink pig sitting on a pair of oversize binoculars; ceramic
    - Pig Hitting a Drum, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 71)
      Ceramic pig in a blue suit hitting a drum
    - Pig with Trotters on Hips, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 14)
      Ceramic, red pig in hat and overalls with trotters on hips
  - Subseries I C: Ceramic Pig Figurines with Floral Designs
    This subseries contains pig figurines that are made entirely or predominantly of ceramic material and display a floral, vine-like, or clover-pattern motif across their bodies.
    - White Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 14)
      White, ceramic pig with red flower and green leaf motif
    - Light Pink Pig with Clover Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 1, Item 19)
      Light pink standing ceramic pig figurine with bloomed clover motif
    - Blue Pig Figurine with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 24)
      Light blue, ceramic pig motif with large ears; pig is standing with an open mouth and with a brown and green floral motif on his back
    - Off-White Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 2)
      Off-white, ceramic standing pig figurine with multi-colored floral motif
    - Pig with Floral Motif and Spread Legs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 5)
      Pink, ceramic pig with yellow floral motif and spread legs
    - Ram-Like Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 10)
      Ram-like, standing, white pig with blue, rust, and green floral motif
    - Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 6, Item 11)
      Ceramic pig with green, red, and white rose motif
    - Pig with Clover on Back, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 8)
      Pink, ceramic pig with clover on back
    - Pink Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 11)
      Pink, ceramic pig with floral motif on back
    - Green Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 16)
      Ceramic, see green pig with blue, yellow, and red spotted and floral motif
    - Pink Pig with Vine Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 13)
      Light pink, ceramic pig with vine motif on back
    - Pig with Green, Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 4)
      White, ceramic pig with pink and green floral motif on its back
    - White Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 21, Item 1)
      White, ceramic pig with black ears and floral motif
    - Pig with Orange and Green Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 18)
      White, ceramic pig with orange and green, floral motif
    - Pig with Pink Flower on Back, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 9)
      Light pink, ceramic pig with pink flower on its back
    - Pig with Blue, Orange, and Green Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 14)
      Ceramic pig with blue, orange, and green floral motif on its back
    - Pig with Long Snout and Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 20)
      Pink, ceramic pig with very long snout and yellow and black floral motif on its back
    - Peach Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 21)
      Peach pig with floral motif along its neck; possibly clay
    - Pig with Faded Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 25)
      Vibrant blue, ceramic pig with faded floral design painted upon its back
    - Pig with Blue Bow and Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 37)
      Black, ceramic pig with blue bow around its neck and a pink, yellow, and green floral design on its back
    - Yellowish Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 51)
      Yellowish, ceramic pig with red, green, and blue floral motif upon its back
    - Pink Floral Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 29)
      Pink standing pig with floral decoration on collar.
  - Subseries I D: Glass Pig Figurines
    This subseries contains pig figurines that are made entirely or predominantly of glass.
    - Off-White Pig with Gold Flecks, circa 1900-2013 (Box 28, Item 2)
      Off-white glass pig with gold fleck detailing
    - Pig with Gold Sparkles, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 4)
      Glass pig figurine with gold sparkle detail
    - Blue and Gold Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 10)
      Gold pig figurine with blue feet and snout
    - Multi-Colored Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 20)
      venetian glass pig with large, blue eyes
    - Pig in Glass Orb, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 14)
      White pig in clear glass orb
    - Blue Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 5)
      Blue glass pig; damaged
    - Pig with Internal Bubbles, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 18)
      Clear glass pig with bubbles inside
    - Pig with Colorful Pattern, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 2)
      Glass pig with bright, colorful pattern
    - Bluish-Purple Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 4)
      Transparent bluish-purple pig in a standing position
    - Red and White Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 6)
      Transparent red and white, glass pig
    - Yellow Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 8)
      Yellow standing glass pig; very fragile
    - Dark Green Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 9)
      Dark green glass pig
    - Vibrant Blue Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 17)
      Bright blue glass pig
    - Pig with Long Snout and Tusks, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 24)
      Dark green, glass pig with long snout and tusks
    - White Pig with Minimal Face, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 22)
      White glass pig with minimal face and prominent tail
    - Clear Glass Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 70)
      Clear glass pig
    - Pig with Blue Detailing, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 1)
      Glass pig with blue detailing
    - White Pig with Red Eyes, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 3)
      White glass pig with red eyes; broken leg
    - Green Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 9)
      Green glass pig; missing feet
    - Red Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 10)
      Red glass pig; broken leg
    - Clear Pig with Floppy Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 11)
      Clear glass pig with floppy, black ears
    - Light Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 13)
      Light pink glass pig with black eyes
    - Pink Pig with Floppy Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 30)
      Pink glass pig with floppy ears in a standing position
    - Pink Glass Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 44-46)
      Set of pink glass pigs with black eyes and floppy ears.
    - White Pig with Pink Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 47)
      White glass pig with pink ears and tail; very fragile.
  - Subseries I E: Wooden Pig Figurines
    This subseries contains pig figurines that are made entirely or predominantly of wood.
    - Round Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 23)
      Round wooden pig painted pink with suede features; damage to one suede ear
    - Dark Brown Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 22)
      Dark brown wooden standing pig
    - Resting Pig with Floppy Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 3)
      Brown wooden pig with floppy ears resting on a base or platform
    - Yellowish Brown Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 13)
      Wooden yellowish brown pig; broken, missing leg
    - Pig with Alert Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 8, Item 6)
      Brown wooden pig with striations on body and alert ears
    - Pig with Floppy Ears, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 10)
      Tan wooden female pig with floppy ears
    - Pig Bust, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 1)
      Wooden, human-like pig bust with open shirt revealing bust; human-like eyes
    - Standing Black Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 40)
      Standing wooden pig painted black
    - Beige Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 34)
      Wooden pig painted beige; leaping position; flaking paint
    - Light Brown Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 40)
      Wooden standing pig that has been glazed a light brown
    - Pig with Mushroom on Back, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 43)
      Wooden pig with clover and mushroom painted on its back; movable legs
    - Pig with Fur, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 49)
      Wooden beige pig with fur body
    - Pink Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 4)
      Wooden pink pig with orange snout
    - Standing Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 12)
      Standing wooden pig
    - Medium Brown Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 18)
      Wooden pig that is standing and medium brown in color
    - Black Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 28)
      Black wooden pig
    - Round, Wooden Pig Figurines, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 40)
      Five round wooden pigs painted pink
    - Dark Brown Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 41)
      Dark brown wooden pig with peg legs and movable ears.
    - Medium Brown Pig with Coin, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 42)
      Medium brown wooden pig with peg legs, removable tail, and coin on its back.
  - Subseries I F: Plastic and Rubber Pig Figurines
    This subseries contains pig figurines that are made entirely or predominantly of plastic or rubber.
    - Pig with Four Leaf Clovers, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 10)
      Rubber beige pig flanked by two green four leaf clovers; very dirty; possibly a dog toy
    - Animated Pig on Blue Platform, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 8)
      Rubber pig on blue stand; rusty crank underneath the platform animates the pig; sticky residue all over; inscription that reads "Pinky Centaur Productions"
    - Yellowish Standing Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 17)
      Yellowish plastic standing pig
    - Pink Pig on Sleigh, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 9)
      Plastic pink pig on plastic rocking sleigh that rattles
    - Purple Pig with Coin, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 24)
      Oval purple pig with peg legs and penny on back; text across side reads "good luck"
    - Gold Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 23)
      Gold, plastic pig; loop on back may indicate the item was a charm for a necklace at one time
    - Beige Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 28)
      Beige standing pig made of plastic
    - Hollow Gold Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 2)
      Hollow gold-colored, plastic pig figurine with the text "Bergen Toy" written inside
    - Beige Standing Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 29)
      Beige-colored standing plastic pig
  - Subseries I G: Cloth Pig Figurines
    This subseries contains pig figurines that are made entirely or predominantly of cloth and stuffing.
    - Crocheted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 30, Item 6)
      Crocheted bluish-gray pig with bell inside; possibly a nursery toy
    - Plush Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 6)
      Light pink plush pig with flower on its head
    - Green Felt Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 18)
      Lime green felt pig with features made of sequins
    - Felt Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 3)
      Green and brown standing felt pig
    - Beige, Felt Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 9)
      Dirty-beige colored felt pig
  - Subseries I H: Metal Pig Figurines
    This subseries contains pig figurines that are made entirely or predominantly of metal.
    - Pig with Pipe on Lily Pad, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 7)
      Beige pig smoking a pipe on lily pad platform; all metal
    - Sitting Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 3, Item 4)
      Heavy plaque of bronze-colored pig sitting on a platform
    - Pig with Sign, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 1)
      Beige, metal pig sitting on base holding a sign that reads "The Wise Pig, Save A Penny Yesterday, Another Save Today, Tomorrow Save Another, To Keep The Wolf Away"
    - Standing Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 12)
      Copper-colored, metal, standing pig
    - Pig with Armor, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 9)
      Black, wooden pig with armor of metal coins strapped to back; loose leg
    - Pig Biting Down on Coin, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 19)
      Pink, metal, sitting pig biting down on a coin
    - Pig Head, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 11)
      Dark gray, metal pig head with back inscription that reads "Ralph Langer Porceltian Club 1903"
    - Black Pig Figurine, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 38)
      Black, aluminum pig figurine.
  - Subseries I I: Stone Pig Figurines
    This subseries contains pig figurines that are carved entirely or predominantly out of stone.
    - Gray Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 7, Item 14)
      Stone, gray, standing pig; broken, missing ear
    - Elephant-Like Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 18)
      Off-white stone, elephant-like pig; housed with wheelbarrow; relationship among items unclear
    - Ivory Pig on Rock, circa 1900-2013 (Box 13, Item 26)
      Hand-carved ivory pig sitting on rock; all beige coloring with prominent veining detail; card explaining significance
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 23)
      Orange and white, stone-carved pig
    - Elephant-Like Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 25)
      Off-white, elephant-like, carved-stone pig
    - Beige Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 27)
      Beige, standing pig carved from stone
    - Grayish-Brown Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 26)
      Grayish-brown, stone-carved pig
    - Brown, Female Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 24)
      Brown, stone-carved, female pig in standing position
    - Pig with Long Ears and Snout, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 52)
      Off-white, stone-carved pig with long ears and snout; broken ear
    - Spotted Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 74)
      Off-white, stone pig with black spots on the grass next to a stone
    - Yellow Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 33)
      Yellow, stone pig
    - Milky White Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 34)
      Milky white colored, stone pig
  - Subseries I J: Marzipan, Soap, and Clay Pig Figurines
    This subseries contains pig figurines that were molded out of marzipan, soap, or clay.
    - Pig with Clover Collar, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 11)
      Peach pig made of soap with clover collar; partially housed in deteriorating plastic
    - University of Arkansas Razorback, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 8)
      Reddish-brown ceramic warthog with the text "Arkansas Razorback" on its back
    - Pig with Groove Detail, circa 1900-2013 (Box 27, Item 17)
      Clay pig figurine with grooves on back
    - Pig with Grooves on Back, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 11)
      Clay brown, hollow, standing pig figurine with striated back design
    - Pig with Clover and Bow, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 14)
      Marzipan pig with clover and pink box
    - Pig with Guitar, circa 1900-2013 (Box 11, Item 16)
      Marzipan pig wearing a hat and playing a guitar; still in solid, plastic box
- Series II: Complex Pig Figurines and Sets
  This series contains figurines of multiple pigs or sets of pigs, which are further grouped into subseries based upon material type and activity depicted.
  - Subseries II A: Ceramic Pig Sets
    This subseries contains complex figurines of multiple pigs or figurine sets that are made entirely or predominantly of ceramic material.
    - Porky Pig and Girlfriend, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 18-19)
      Beige, ceramic pig set of Porky Pig and beige female pig with blonde hair in a blue dress. Female pig is not Petunia Pig
    - Three Little Pigs in Bed, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 32)
      Ceramic figurine of Three Little Pigs in bed with blue blanket
    - Fighting Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 30)
      Ceramic figurine of two white pigs fighting
    - Set of Off-White Pigs with Floral Motifs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 25, Item 15, 31-32)
      Set of off-white, ceramic pigs with pink, blue, and floral motifs on their backs; all pigs have open mouths exposing a pink tongue
    - Pig Band, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 26-30)
      Ceramic set of dark beige pigs singing and playing various instruments in red, blue, and green outfits
    - Set of Three Beige Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 20, 33-34)
      Set of three very light beige, ceramic pigs with gray shading; two standing and one sitting
    - Set of Pink Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 21, 23)
      Set of two pink, ceramic pigs with shaded snout, ears, and tail; one sleeping and the other sitting down with large, blue eyes
    - Set of Mouse-Like Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 21-22)
      Set of two brown, ceramic, mouse-like, sitting pig figurines with pink ears
    - Set of Off-White Pigs with Prominent Eyelashes, circa 1900-2013 (Box 27, Item 18, 21)
      Set of two off-white, ceramic pigs with yellowish shading and downturned heads with brown facial features and prominent eyelashes
    - Set of Pink Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 17)
      Set of one larger, ceramic, pink pig and three smaller piglets
    - Pigs in Shed Eating, circa 1900-2013 (Box 8, Item 2)
      Two pigs poking out of shed eating from a log-like trough; ceramic
    - Pigs in Front of Hat, circa 1900-2013 (Box 22, Item 12)
      Two pink, ceramic pigs in front of an oversize, green top hat
    - Pigs in Purse, circa 1900-2013 (Box 10, Item 9)
      Two pigs in green clutch or purse with gold detailing; ceramic
    - Spotted Pig with Piglets, circa 1900-2013 (Box 12, Item 11)
      Grayish-blue, ceramic pig tending to five piglets
    - Pig with Gold Piglets, circa 1900-2013 (Box 14, Item 11)
      Bluish-gray, ceramic pig with two golden piglets
    - Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 9, Item 21)
      White and blue, ceramic pig with floral motif on back, associated with pig in box 24, item 20.
    - Pigs Eating From Bowl, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 2)
      Three pink, ceramic pigs eating from a bowl on the grass
    - Pigs in Trunk, circa 1900-2013 (Box 23, Item 21)
      Two pink pigs in green and white trunk; ceramic
    - Pigs with Doe Eyes, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 15)
      Three brown and pink pigs with doe eyes; one sleeping; ceramic figurine; fragile
    - Set of Sitting Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 34-38)
      Set of two brown and off-white, ceramic pigs sitting upright; pink-colored features; damaged
    - Peering Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 16, Item 19)
      Two, pink pigs peering from orange and green trunk; ceramic
    - Reddish Pig with Piglets, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Item 13)
      Reddish pig chained to two reddish piglets
    - Chained Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 14)
      Pink pig chained to piglets
    - Cow-Like Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 17)
      Ceramic, cow-like, prancing pig with pink snout, related to pig in Box 17, item 29.
    - Floral Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 27)
      Two off-white pigs with pink flowers on their backs; ceramic
    - Set of White Pigs with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 3-4)
      Set of two white, ceramic pigs with floral patterns upon their backs
    - Set of Dark Brown and White Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 57-61)
      Set of dark brown and white pigs with pink ears; two are large while three are smaller; ceramic
    - Sow and Piglet in Box, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 73)
      Ceramic sow and her piglet in a wooden box; both pigs are pink
    - Yellowish Pigs Set, circa 1900-2013 (Box 18, Item 77-78)
      Set of yellowish pigs with green spots, one sitting and one standing; both ceramic
    - Striated Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 29, Item 83-85)
      Series of brown, striated pigs; ceramic; some missing limbs
    - Spotted Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 19-23)
      Tan and dark brown spotted pigs; made of ceramic
    - Adult Pigs and Piglets, circa 1900-2013 (Box 19, Item 48-53)
      Three adult pigs and three piglets standing; one pig lighter than others; made in Germany.
    - Cow-Like Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 20, Item 17)
    - Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1990-2013 (Box 25, Item 20)
      White and blue, ceramic pig with floral motif on back, associated with pig in box 9, item 21.
    - Three Little Pigs in Clothing, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 11)
      Large, ceramic figurine of three little pigs in human clothing
    - Cow-Like Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 15, Item 42)
      Small ceramic standing cow-like pig with pink snout.
    - Pig with Floral Motif, circa 1900-2013 (Box 24, Item 20)
    - Cow-Like Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      Ceramic, cow-like, prancing pig with pink snout, related to pig in Box 20, item 17.
  - Subseries II B: Ceramic Pig Figurines with Humans
    This subseries contains pig figurines engaging with humans and are made entirely or predominately of ceramic.
    - Boy with Mangalica Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 1, Item 1)
      Complex, round, ceramic figurine with a boy in a white shirt, white pants, blue vest, and brown hat playing an instrument with two brown Mangalica pigs on the grass
    - Pig with Man and Woman, circa 1900-2013 (Box 2, Item 9)
      Pink, ceramic pig at the feet of a man and a woman on a base that reads "Pat's Last March"
    - Female Figure with Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 3, Item 1)
      Ceramic, female figurine in yellow hat and white dress holding a basket with a pink pig at her feet on the grass
    - Young Child with Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 26, Item 3)
      Young child with rosy cheeks holding two pigs with charcoal-colored spots; ceramic
    - Man Feeding Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 4, Item 1)
      Man in violet suit feeding two pigs at a trough; ceramic; damaged
    - Man and Woman Kissing with Pig, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 7)
      Pastel-toned, ceramic man and woman kissing with a pig at the foot of the man
    - Chef Holding Pigs Set, circa 1900-2013 (Box 5, Item 9)
      ceramic chef holding pigs set related to box 10 item 10.
    - Woman with Pigs, circa 1900-2013 (Box 28, Item 17)